

KAMIL RĄPAŁA

IT SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER/SCRUM MASTER

SUMMARY

Over 8 years I have been expanding my knowledge and acquiring skills in the ecommerce / IT industry. In my actual job, I am a project manager/scrum master and I put the satisfaction of my clients on the 1st place. I secure the continuity of online sales through effective technical support. I work with well-known online stores, supervise their development and security in the successive use of the Magento, PIM and Presta systems.

Gallup - 1. Achiever - 2. Individualization - 3. Strategic - 4. Communication - 5. Learner

DISC - Dominance - 40% / Influence - 35% / Conscientiousness - 15% / Steadiness - 10%

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Project management
- Content Creation
- Public Relations
- Website Management
- Digital Analytic Tools
- Graphic Design
- Strong Communication Skills
- Team management
- Time management
- Project planning
- E-commerce
- *UX*
- Jira
- QA manual test with creating a scenarios
- Magento 1&2, Pimcore, Hyva PrestaShop, Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Gimp

Certificates (part)

- Google PMP
- Pimcore Consultant
- Newrelic Full Stack Observability Practitioner
- Generative AI Overview PMI
- PSM

CONTACT DETAILS:

Telephone: 535 422 062

Email: rapala.kamil@gmail.com

City: Tarnów

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/kamilrąpała Portfolio: kamilr96.github.io/Portfolio/#home

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Gate-Software

IT PROJECT MANAGER - (JULY 2020 - PRESENT)

- Establishing and maintaining customer relationships
- Analysis of customer requirements
- Creating and assigning tasks
- Coordinating task progress
- · Controlling the budget
- Creating documentation
- Team management
- Cooperation with external companies
- Magento consulting
- UX design/Creating mockups
- Code Review (Gitlab)
- Preparing training
- Manual testing

Everything is preserved in Agile methodology and SOLID-based scrum teams

PMI PC Krakow Branch

EDUCATION LEADER - (JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT)

- Developing concepts, programs, writing scripts, conducting cultural classes, workshops and other forms of educational and cultural activities
- Participation and realisation in popular science shows at PMI meetings
- Seeking and implementing new forms of media and new cultural activities
- Development of scenarios for thematic educational paths
- Preparation of schedules, scenarios, descriptions and other documentation
- Creating offers and applications within the university
- Keeping statistics

Medpak

E-COMMERCE MANAGER, (AUGUST 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2020)

- Editing and adding new descriptions with photos to MedPak blog on the site, powered by PrestaShop
- Adding new products in the baselinker panel based on wordpress, to create html-based auctions at the sales channels Allegro, amazon, ebay, empik
- Using a customer service (SubiektGT) as a database to add new products from invoices and deliveries, checking prices, determine the margin for a given product
- Analyzing the Allegro market for the health category through TradeWatch Creating complex lists in Excel
- Using slack, teams and trello in communications, presentation
- Contact with goods suppliers and clients
- Searching for new products
- Spotting and fixing bugs
- Social media developments

dlaGentlemana

UX DESIGNER/ GRAPHIC DESIGNER - (AUGUST 2019 - APRIL 2020)

- Creating graphic designs for Facebook / Instagram
- promotional / advertising clips
- Taking care of the company's social profiles and other places of content marketing activities, such as blogs, newsletters, site and e-mailing campaigns

TonGraph

PROJECT MANAGER & UX DESIGNER (AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2018)

- Team management based on kanban boards.
- creating graphics for music bands, logos for creators from streaming channels, ads, banners or promoting specific brands for online stores.
 Moreover, preparation shorts intro / outro films and preparation of UX mockups for web applications and websites.
- Creating graphic designs for Facebook / Instagram
- promotional / advertising clips
- Using slack, teams and trello in communications, presentation.
- Contact with clients.

ACADEMIC HISTORY

Cracow University of Economics

Applied Computer Science (2019 - 2021) - Master degree

State Higher Vocational School in Tarnow

Applied Computer Science (2015 - 2019) - Bachelor in Engineering of Computer Science

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).